[{"answer": "I don't care what makes you so curious (ph).", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Who walks away with the gold guy?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think it surprised the legal experts.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "What's the significance of Pistorius getting bail at this stage, do you think?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "It's not.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Should we read anything into that or is that a consistent thing in South African law?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Is that the sense you're getting among South Africans?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "No, like I said before, the onus is on Oscar.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Do you have absolute confidence that Oscar is telling the truth?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "It's basically used to fight the means of fatigue and tiredness.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "What is that?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Look, that's the magistrate's decision and what the magistrate wants during this bail, after this bail application.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "What can you tell me about Oscar and alcohol?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "I'm sure when he goes out and goes for dinner with his friends and family, we'll have an occasional drink, but he's not an alcoholic if that's what you're asking.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "He does drink alcohol then?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "We don't know.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Are you ready for the next stage?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I have to read the conditions.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What are your concerns?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Look, I mean, that's obviously something he would do in his private time or he's off time.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Would you say the reality is he would have alcohol just not to access?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Briefly, I spoke to his brother, I called, just to send my wishes and that my thoughts are with him and his family as they are going through a hard time.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Have you reached out to him or any of his family?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Piers, I didn't know him intimately.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "And if you did, what did you make of him?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "I tried to keep my discussions with Reeva on a business level.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Had Reeva given you any indication of any problems with Oscar at all in the whole time that you knew she was seeing him?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "She was on the brink of explosion.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "How big could she have become do you think?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I think the magistrate raised substantial questions today.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Why don't you believe him?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, there are holes in his story and if the holes are validated by the empirical evidence, by the forensic evidence, he'll be convicted.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, your response to that?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Absolutely, because motive is not necessary to prove.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Without that, is it fair to convict him?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "I don't even know how to go backwards.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Alan, we left viewers in a cliffhanger there, you were accused of going backwards, backtracking, what was your response to Gloria?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "That's like apples and oranges.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Why did he have to fire four shots?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "The four shots thing I find a bit of a misnomer in terms of an argument against Pistorius, if he genuinely thought it was an intruder who is about to attack him, or fear for his life, you look at the number of cases in America where there are states for stand your ground.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Why not just one shot?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "What are you saying, Gloria, it's based on calm, rational thought.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Why didn't he see if his girlfriend was OK and help her to run out the door?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Isn't the reality in the heat of the moment, nobody knows how someone is going to behave?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I don't think the public image is misleading.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Is it a lot more volatile than we may imagine?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "I think he was obsessed with his own safety and his own vulnerability.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Does he like them to the point of obsession, I mean, how would you describe his relationship with guns?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "When I was with him, it was in the lead-up to the Olympics, to the London Olympics, and I think he had some wine around the house, but he very specifically told me he wasn't drinking at that time in those months, because he said I train so hard, alcohol has the impact of diminishing your training a little bit, and why should I give up anything, even for a glass of wine, because I am working so hard to be as fit as I can be.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Did you get the sense that occasionally he would drink a lot?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "I didn't.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "And in terms of his behavior around women, did you see anything untoward in that regard?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I hear the length is quite long.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "What do you think of skewing it towards a more musical performance?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "They are balancing it with having the cast of \"The Avengers\" present, Daniel Radcliffe will be presenting, as well as there's a tribute to the 50th anniversary of James Bond.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Ben, the musical stuff is fine, but if you're skewing it to a younger demographic audience, is it sensible?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "But do you see any surprises there?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "My favorite film of the year.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Another mention for Quvenzhane, the young girl?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Short answer, no.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Are we all agreed?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I can't bet against Steven Spielberg.", "docId": "130222pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Where's your money, then?", "qSentId": 576}]